Eralp ÖZCAN

Full Stack Developer | Frontend Developer

■ eralpozcans@gmail.com in eralpozcan eralpozcan www.eralpozcan.dev

● eralpozcan eralpozcan listanbul

Profile

I'm currently a Full Stack Developer. I have been developing myself in the field of Frontend, Backend since 2021. Previously, I had an adventure in artificial intelligence and data analysis for 2 years. I enjoy working in the software field as I have transitioned from the automation field. Since I have the opportunity to work in many interdisciplinary fields, I can easily adapt. In my spare time, I like reading, playing the piano, traveling and exploring new places.

Professional Experience

Frontend Developer, Protein Tech

10/2022 – present Istanbul, Turkey

- I'm developing a stock tracking / cost management web application called Simpra Inventory with Vue.js.
- I'm in an agile (scrum) team thus well familiar with the methodology, principals and rules.
- Working with industry standard tools such as Jira, Swagger, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Postman, ESLint, SonarQube; and actively implementing outputs from Figma.

Full Stack Developer, Arma Group Holding

08/2022 – 10/2022 Gebze,Kocaeli, Turkey

- Development of projects Vue3 and Node.js(Fastify)
- Software development for Ads-Advertise platform
- Software development Drive platform
- Development of with Sequelize ORM and PostgreSQL

Freelancer, Upwork

08/2021 - 10/2022

- Development of projects with HTML CSS and JS, Vue
- Software development for gaming platform with Lua and SQL.
- Data Analysis and Visualization

Education

Mechatronics Engineering, Karabuk University

2013 - 2019

 Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning Laboratory. I have been in various studies. This ResistorNet-DirencNet academic poster. Turkey

• I have gained experience and knowledge about autonomous systems, automation systems and mechatronics systems.

Business Administration and Management, Anadolu University

2017 - 2023

Cost, Organization Development and Entrepreneurship.

Turkey

Skills

Vue.js

- Vuex
- Vuetify

Node.is

- RestAPI
- MongoDB
- Postgresql

Front-end

- HTML
- SCSS
- Javacript

Organizations

English Hungarian B1 A1	
Languages	
 ResistorNet-DirencNet, IDSEW'18 Creation of resistance data and classification by Deep Learning. I did the research and development part of the project. We created the data with Deep Learning Lab. members. Dataset is in Kaggle. 	06/2018
Publications	
 ResistorNet-DirencNet, Researcher Creation of resistance data and classification by Deep Learning. I did the research and development part of the project. We created the data with Deep Learning Lab. members. Dataset is in Kaggle. 	05/2018 – 06/2018
Reinforcement Learning Workgroup • Multi-armed bandits workshop	07/2018 – 07/2019
Commite, Project FounderOpen Source Social Media For DevelopersVue.js,Node.js,Socket.io	06/2022 – present
Projects	
 Deep Learning Türkiye, Deep Learning Researcher Volunteer (December 2017- June 2020) Reinforcement Learning workgroup. (December-2018 -June 2019) 	12/2017 – 06/2020
 World Food Programme, Bootcamp Assistant React.js Bootcamp with the Kodluyoruz Flutter Bootcamp with the Kodluyoruz 	06/2022 – 09/2022
 Yapay Zekâ Araştırma İnisiyatifi, Al Researcher at Deep Learning Team Open-source Academic Research and Development Platform on Al Technologies 	07/2020 – 08/2023
 Kodluyoruz, Master Assistant Master Assistant Mentor Bootcamp Acceleration Mentor Protein Full Stack Bootcamp Assistant (Vue.js) Gelecek Varlık Full Stack Bootcamp Assistant (React.jsNet) 	06/2021 – 09/2023 Turkey